Guide to the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust Records, 1975-2021 CTC.2000.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Finance, 1984-1996; VII.
  - 1099s, 1989 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - 1099 information, 1990 (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - 1099 information, 1992 (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - 1099 miscellaneous forms, 1991 (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Account analysis statement, July 1992 (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - Accounting staff meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Administrative operating fund 1990 summary budget status report, 1990-1991 (Box 210, Folder 7-13)
  - Administrative reports and notes, 1987-1990 (Box 211, Folder 1-3)
  - Annual campaign, 1992 (Box 211, Folder 4-5)
  - Annual campaign, November 1993 (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - Annual campaign first quarter, 1994 (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Annual campaign bank statement, 1994 (Box 211, Folder 8-10)
  - Art Cinema open invoices, 1990 (Box 211, Folder 11)
  - Art services open invoices, 1990-1991 (Box 211, Folder 12-13)
  - Art services paid invoices, 1991 (Box 211, Folder 14)
  - Arts Pittsburgh This Week open invoices, 1990 (Box 211, Folder 15)
  - Audit committee meeting, April 21 1987 (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Benedum Center box office bank statement, February 1994 (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - Benedum Center box office bank statement, September 1994 (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - Benedum Center budget materials, 1988 (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - Benedum Center capital, June 1990 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - Benedum Center capital, July 1990 (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - Benedum Center capital, 1992 (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - Benedum Center capital, June 1992 (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - Benedum Center capital, July 1992 (Box 212, Folder 9)
  - Benedum Center capital, November 1993 (Box 212, Folder 10)
  - Benedum Center capital, January 1994 (Box 212, Folder 11)
  - Benedum Center capital, February 1994 (Box 212, Folder 12)
  - Benedum Center capital, March 1994 (Box 212, Folder 13)
  - Benedum Center computer and data processing, 1987-1988 (Box 212, Folder 14)
  - Benedum Center equipment maintenance services, 1987-1988 (Box 212, Folder 15)
  - Benedum Center expenses, 1984-1988 (Box 212, Folder 16)
  - Benedum Center invoice log, 1996 (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - Benedum Center operating cash receipts, January 1994 (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Benedum Center operating cash receipts, February 1994 (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - Benedum Center operating fund re-projected budget, December 1990 (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Benedum Center project notes meetings and letters, 1987-1988 (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - Benedum Center rental information, 1993 (Box 213, Folder 6)
  - Board of trustees and executive committee materials and minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 213, Folder 7)
  - Budget status report, December 1994 (Box 213, Folder 8)
  - Budget status report, September 1995 (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - Budget status report, October 1995 (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - Budget status report, May 1996 (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - Budget status report, August 1996 (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - Budgetary materials, 1987-1989 (Box 214, Folder 5-6)
  - Capital campaign, June 1990 (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - Capital campaign, July 1990 (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - Capital projects first quarter, 1995 (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - Capital projects second quarter, 1995 (Box 215, Folder 4)
  - Capital projects third quarter, 1995 (Box 215, Folder 5)
  - Clark building easement, November 1987 (Box 215, Folder 6)
  - Consulting services, 1991 (Box 215, Folder 7)
  - Consulting services, 1992 (Box 215, Folder 8)
  - Cultural tourism paid invoices, 1991 (Box 215, Folder 9)
  - Daily donor logs, 1992 (Box 215, Folder 10)
  - District development, June 1990 (Box 215, Folder 11)
  - District development, July 1990 (Box 215, Folder 12)
  - District development, June 1992 (Box 215, Folder 13)
  - District development, July 1992 (Box 215, Folder 14)
  - District development, November 1993 (Box 215, Folder 15)
  - District development first quarter, 1994 (Box 215, Folder 16)
  - District development second quarter, 1994 (Box 215, Folder 17)
  - District development, 1995 (Box 215, Folder 18)
  - District development first quarter, 1995 (Box 215, Folder 19)
  - District development second quarter, 1995 (Box 215, Folder 20)
  - District development third quarter, 1995 (Box 215, Folder 21)
  - District development bank statement, January 1994 (Box 215, Folder 22)
  - District development bank statement, February 1994 (Box 215, Folder 23)
  - District development bank statement, March 1994 (Box 215, Folder 24)
  - Facility operations bank statement, December 1994 (Box 215, Folder 25)
  - Facility operations bank statement, January 1995 (Box 215, Folder 26)
  - Facility operations bank statement, February 1995 (Box 216, Folder 1)
  - Facility operations bank statement, March 1995 (Box 216, Folder 2)
  - Facility operations bank statement, February 1996 (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - Facility operations bank statement, March 1996 (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - Financial statements, 1990-1992 (Box 216, Folder 5)
  - Fulton capital, June 1990 (Box 216, Folder 6)
  - Fulton capital, July 1990 (Box 216, Folder 7)
  - Fulton capital first quarter, 1992 (Box 216, Folder 8)
  - Fulton capital second quarter, 1992 (Box 216, Folder 9)
  - Fulton capital, June 1992 (Box 216, Folder 10)
  - Fulton capital, July 1992 (Box 216, Folder 11)
  - Fulton capital, November 1993 (Box 216, Folder 12)
  - Fulton capital first quarter, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 13)
  - Fulton capital second quarter, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 14)
  - Fulton capital bank statement, January 1994 (Box 216, Folder 15)
  - Fulton capital bank statement, February 1994 (Box 216, Folder 16)
  - Fulton capital bank statement, March 1994 (Box 216, Folder 17)
  - Fulton open invoices, 1991 (Box 216, Folder 18)
  - Fulton operating, June 1990 (Box 216, Folder 19)
  - Fulton operating, July 1990 (Box 216, Folder 20)
  - Fulton operating first quarter, 1992 (Box 216, Folder 21)
  - Fulton operating second quarter, 1994 (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - Fulton operating, June 1992 (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - Fulton operating, July 1992 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - Fulton operating, November 1993 (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Fulton operating first quarter, 1994 (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - Fulton operating second quarter, 1994 (Box 217, Folder 6)
  - Fulton operations, 1995 (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - Fulton paid invoices, 1991 (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - Fulton rental information, 1993 (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - Funded depreciation, June 1990 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Funded depreciation, July 1990 (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - Funded depreciation, June 1992 (Box 218, Folder 6)
  - Funded depreciation, July 1992 (Box 218, Folder 7)
  - Funded depreciation, November 1993 (Box 218, Folder 8)
  - General annual campaign, January 1995 (Box 218, Folder 9)
  - General annual campaign, February 1995 (Box 218, Folder 10)
  - General annual campaign, March 1995 (Box 218, Folder 11)
  - General operating fund, January 1995 (Box 218, Folder 12)
  - General operating fund, February 1995 (Box 218, Folder 13)
  - General operating fund, March 1995 (Box 218, Folder 14)
  - Horizon: the magazine of the arts guide to creative media planning (Box 218, Folder 15)
  - Internal memos, 1989 (Box 218, Folder 16)
  - Journal entries administration, 1992-1993 (Box 219, Folder 1-4)
  - Journal entries district development, 1992-1993 (Box 219, Folder 5-8)
  - Ledgers - Benedum Center capital company 3, 1990 (Box 220, Folder 1)
  - Ledgers - Benedum Center capital preliminary, 1990 (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - Ledgers - District development company 8, 1990 (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - Ledgers - District development preliminary, 1990 (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - Ledgers - Fulton capital preliminary, 1990 (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - Ledgers - Fulton operating preliminary, 1990 (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Ledgers - Fulton operating company 5, 1990 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - Ledgers - Fulton capital company 6, 1990 (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - Ledgers - TIX booth preliminary, 1990 (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Ledgers - TIX booth company 7, 1990 (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - Ledgers - Trust operating administration preliminary, 1990 (Box 221, Folder 5-6)
  - Legal fees, 1987-1989 (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - Lisa J.L. Caswell Benedum Center budget projections, 1988-1989 (Box 222, Folder 2-3)
  - Lisa J.L. Caswell budget compilation, 1989 (Box 222, Folder 4)
  - Lisa J.L. Caswell budget copies, 1989 (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - Lisa J.L. Caswell file, 1986 (Box 222, Folder 6)
  - Lisa J.L. Caswell file, 1987 (Box 222, Folder 7-10)
  - Lisa J.L. Caswell file - First quarter, 1988 (Box 222, Folder 11)
  - Lisa J.L. Caswell file - Fourth quarter, 1988 (Box 222, Folder 12)
  - Lisa J.L. Caswell file - Fourth quarter, 1989 (Box 223, Folder 1)
  - Lisa J.L. Caswell file - First quarter, 1991 (Box 223, Folder 2)
  - Lisa J.L. Caswell file - Second quarter, 1991 (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Lisa J.L. Caswell office correspondence, 1986-1991 (Box 223, Folder 4-8)
  - Mailing lists, 1984-1987 (Box 223, Folder 9)
  - Memos received, 1993-1994 (Box 223, Folder 10)
  - Notes from telephone meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 223, Folder 11)
  - Notes with Carol Brown, 1987-1988 (Box 223, Folder 12-13)
  - Notes with Carol Brown, 1989-1991 (Box 224, Folder 1-3)
  - Open invoices, 1993-1994 (Box 224, Folder 4-5)
  - Organizational chart, 1993 (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - Participation fee open invoices, 1990 (Box 224, Folder 7)
  - Participation fee open invoices, 1994 (Box 224, Folder 8)
  - Petty cash distribution, 1994 (Box 224, Folder 9)
  - Pittsburgh Filmmakers at the Fulton, 1987-1988 (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - Pittsburgh Magazine media kit (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - Pittsburgh Symphony Society check request forms, 1992-1993 (Box 225, Folder 3)
  - Pittsburgh Treasurer invoices, 1993 (Box 225, Folder 4)
  - Poster fees paid invoices, 1991 (Box 225, Folder 5)
  - Poster fees paid invoices, 1994 (Box 225, Folder 6)
  - Program advertising paid invoices, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 7)
  - Programming and scheduling policy, 1991 (Box 225, Folder 8)
  - Sales tax, 1993 (Box 225, Folder 9)
  - Sandy Snee accounting manager correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 225, Folder 10-11)
  - Shared advertising paid invoices, 1991 (Box 225, Folder 12)
  - Staff meeting notes, 1987-1988 (Box 225, Folder 13)
  - Staff meeting notes, 1989-1991 (Box 226, Folder 1-3)
  - TIX fund, June 1990 (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - TIX fund, July 1990 (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - TIX fund, June 1992 (Box 226, Folder 6)
  - TIX fund, July 1992 (Box 226, Folder 7-8)
  - TIX fund, November 1993 (Box 226, Folder 9)
  - TIX fund, 1994 (Box 226, Folder 10)
  - Trust administration paid invoices, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 11)
  - Trust operating, June 1990 (Box 226, Folder 12)
  - Trust operating, July 1990 (Box 226, Folder 13)
  - Trust operating, January 1992 (Box 226, Folder 14)
  - Trust operating, February 1992 (Box 226, Folder 15)
  - Trust operating, June 1992 (Box 226, Folder 16)
  - Trust operating, July 1992 (Box 226, Folder 17-18)
  - Trust operating, November 1993 (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - Trust operating, August 1994 (Box 227, Folder 2)
  - Trust operating, September 1994 (Box 227, Folder 3)
  - Trust operating, October 1994 (Box 227, Folder 4)
  - Trust operating, November 1994 (Box 227, Folder 5)
  - Trust operating, 1995 (Box 227, Folder 6)
  - Trust operating paid invoices, 1994 (Box 227, Folder 7)
  - Utilization statistics for the Benedum Center and Fulton, 1992-1993 (Box 227, Folder 8)
  - Wood Street Galleries deposits first quarter, 1994 (Box 227, Folder 9)
  - Wood Street Galleries deposits second quarter, 1994 (Box 227, Folder 10)
  - Wood Street Galleries invoice logs, July-December 1996 (Box 227, Folder 11)
  - Wood Street Galleries operating, 1995 (Box 227, Folder 12)
  - Wood Street Galleries statements, 1994 (Box 227, Folder 13-15)
- Marketing, 1975-1999; VIII.
  The series contains promotional and marketing materials for the Trust's various performing arts series' - the Pittsburgh Broadway Series, Arts Blastoff! Live on Stage, Voices of a New Millennium, the Street Fair, and others. Several productions of the Pittsburgh Broadway Series are more thoroughly documented, these being the Phantom of the Opera, les Miserables, Show Boat, and Miss Saigon. Also within this series are sets of marketing files for most of the productions that were performed between 1989-1999. This series also includes a five year run of newspaper clippings.
  - General Marketing files, 1975-1999; 1.
    These are the marketing department's general office files. Most notable among the files here are the materials relating to the opening and exhibits of the Wood Street Galleries and the joint promotions between the Cultural Trust and the Pittsburgh Downtown Partnership. These files are arranged in alphabetical order by subject.
    - AMC Benedum the King and I, May 1996 (Box 228, Folder 1)
    - AMC Movie Palace Memories, 1996 (Box 228, Folder 2)
    - Advertising budget and expenses, 1994-1998 (Box 228, Folder 3)
    - Alvin Alley Dance Theater, 1995-1996 (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - America's Smithsonian, 1996 (Box 228, Folder 5)
    - ArtsNet, June 1995 (Box 228, Folder 6)
    - Arts and Chat, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 7)
    - Arts Happy Hour postcards, 1992 (Box 228, Folder 8)
    - Arts Surveys, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 9)
    - Avenue of the Arts Festival, 1998 (Box 228, Folder 10)
    - Benedum Center construction party, 1987 (Box 228, Folder 11)
    - Benedum Center fifth anniversary, 1992 (Box 228, Folder 12)
    - Benedum Center first five years, 1992 (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - Benedum Center first year attendance, 1988 (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - Benedum Center first year newspaper clippings, 1988 (Box 229, Folder 3)
    - Benedum Center HVAC advertisement (Box 229, Folder 4)
    - Benedum Center opening gala press release, 1987 (Box 229, Folder 5)
    - Benedum Center press briefing, 1987 (Box 229, Folder 6)
    - Benedum Center press conference Paul G. Benedum remarks, September 16 1987 (Box 229, Folder 7)
    - Benedum Center press conference Paul R. Jenkins remarks (Box 229, Folder 8)
    - Benedum Center press conference Robert Dickey III remarks, October 4 1987 (Box 229, Folder 9)
    - Benedum Center window displays, 1997 (Box 229, Folder 10)
    - Bradley Brown Design Group, February 1995 (Box 229, Folder 11)
    - Broadway Presents, 1994-1997 (Box 229, Folder 12-14)
    - Carol Brown interview requests, 1998 (Box 229, Folder 15)
    - Budget status reports and compilation information, 1991 (Box 229, Folder 16)
    - Byham Theater small non-profit lease information, October 1997 (Box 229, Folder 17)
    - Carnegie Library of Pittsburgh, 1993-1994 (Box 229, Folder 18)
    - Carnegie Mellon University project Ace Amusements building, 1995-1996 (Box 229, Folder 19)
    - City of Pittsburgh special events permit application (Box 229, Folder 20)
    - Communications division planning session, 1998 (Box 229, Folder 21)
    - ComDoc's consultative reprographic study proposal (Box 229, Folder 22)
    - Commercial Printing Services, March 1995 (Box 229, Folder 23)
    - Computer survey arts services questionnaire, 1992 (Box 229, Folder 24)
    - Creative achievement awards, 1991-1992 (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - Creative achievement awards, 1994-1996 (Box 230, Folder 2-4)
    - Creative achievement award Natalie Petesch, 1991 (Box 230, Folder 5)
    - Creative achievement award Reza Vali, 1992 (Box 230, Folder 6)
    - Creative achievement award David Stock, 1992 (Box 230, Folder 7)
    - Creative achievement award Lorraine Vullo, 1992 (Box 230, Folder 8)
    - Creative achievement award Tim Kaulen, 1993-1994 (Box 230, Folder 9)
    - Creative achievement award Mark Taylor, 1993-1994 (Box 230, Folder 10)
    - Creative achievement award Albert French, 1995 (Box 230, Folder 11)
    - Creative achievement award Helena Ruoti, 1995 (Box 230, Folder 12)
    - Cultural City USA campaign, 1995-1996 (Box 230, Folder 13)
    - Cultural City USA logos, 1995-1996 (Box 230, Folder 14)
    - Cultural District calendar of events, 1996-1997 (Box 230, Folder 15)
    - Cultural Trust ten years of success, 2000 (Box 230, Folder 16)
    - Cultural tourism ad placement schedule, 1991-1992 (Box 231, Folder 1)
    - Cultural tourism advertising, 1990-1997 (Box 231, Folder 2)
    - Cultural tourism advertisements, 1990-1991 (Box 231, Folder 3-4)
    - Cultural tourism arts weekend advertisement, 1991 (Box 231, Folder 5)
    - Cultural tourism background information, 1988-1989 (Box 231, Folder 6)
    - Cultural tourism brochure purchase orders, 1990-1991 (Box 231, Folder 7)
    - Cultural tourism brochures, 1993-1994 (Box 231, Folder 8)
    - Cultural tourism calendar and promotional materials, 1994-1995 (Box 231, Folder 9)
    - Cultural tourism charter service, 1991-1992 (Box 231, Folder 10)
    - Cultural tourism display booth, 1991 (Box 231, Folder 11)
    - Cultural tourism newspaper clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 231, Folder 12)
    - Cultural tourism other cities' visitors guide, 1994-1995 (Box 231, Folder 13)
    - Cultural tourism Pennsylvania travel supplement, 1990 (Box 232, Folder 1)
    - Cultural tourism Pennsylvania visitors guide, 1994-1996 (Box 232, Folder 2)
    - Cultural tourism program, 1990-1994 (Box 232, Folder 3-4)
    - Cultural tourism program, 1996-1997 (Box 232, Folder 5)
    - Cultural tourism program evaluation, 1991 (Box 232, Folder 6)
    - Cultural tourism reports, 1990-1994 (Box 232, Folder 7)
    - Cultural tourism telephone, 1990-1993 (Box 232, Folder 8)
    - Development plan materials and publications, 1984-1990 (Box 232, Folder 9)
    - Development plan newspaper clippings, 1989-1991 (Box 232, Folder 10)
    - Diet Coke Pittsburgh Broadway Series 92-93 season press releases, 1992-1993 (Box 232, Folder 11)
    - Diet Coke Pittsburgh Broadway Series 92-93 season recap report, 1992-1993 (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - Display windows, July 1997 (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - Downtown plan press conference, December 1990 (Box 233, Folder 3)
    - Draft strategic plan, July 1991 (Box 233, Folder 4)
    - Duquesne University, May 1996 (Box 233, Folder 5)
    - Edge of Art-Works, 1994 (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - Ellis School tour, September 1996 (Box 233, Folder 7)
    - Enertex Marketing, 1996-1998 (Box 233, Folder 8-10)
    - External publicity, 1987-1992 (Box 233, Folder 11)
    - Facade renovation projects, 1995 (Box 233, Folder 12)
    - Facade renovation reception, 1996 (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - Pinkie Familoni, 1995-1996 (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - First Night, 1995-1996 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - Fulton Theater clean up, 1989 (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - the Fulton Theater an Evaluation and Recommendations by MacLachlan Cornelius and Filoni Inc, November 1984 (Box 234, Folder 5)
    - Fulton Theater facts and scheduling procedures, 1991-1992 (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - Fulton Theater Identity Proposal by Agnew Moyer Smith Inc, January 30 1991 (Box 234, Folder 7)
    - Fulton Theater newspaper clippings, 1987-1989 (Box 234, Folder 8)
    - Fulton Theater opening press kit, 1991 (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - Fulton Theater opening promotional materials and newspaper clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - Fulton Theater promotional materials, 1988-1990 (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - the Role of the Fulton Theatre and Smaller Performing Arts Facilities in Pittsburgh's Downtown Cultural District by Roger Morgan Studio Inc, September 1987 (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - Gargaro productions, 1993-1996 (Box 235, Folder 5)
    - Goodspeed Opera Project, 1998 (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - Grantmakers weekend, 1996 (Box 235, Folder 7)
    - Graphics (Box 235, Folder 8)
    - Greater Pittsburgh Chamber of Commerce visual encyclopedia (Box 235, Folder 9)
    - Greater Pittsburgh Convention and Visitors Bureau, 1994-1996 (Box 235, Folder 10)
    - Greater Pittsburgh Convention and Visitors Bureau calendars, 1994-1999 (Box 235, Folder 11)
    - Greater Pittsburgh Convention and Visitors Bureau group tour guide, 1995-1996 (Box 235, Folder 12)
    - Greater Pittsburgh Convention and Visitors Bureau marketing planner, 1994-1996 (Box 235, Folder 13)
    - Greater Pittsburgh Convention and Visitors Bureau reports, 1991-1996 (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Greater Pittsburgh Convention and Visitors Bureau visitors guides, 1993-1995 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - Harris Theater opening, 1995 (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - Independent Ad Specialties (Box 236, Folder 4)
    - Institutional advertising, 1998-1999 (Box 236, Folder 5)
    - Institutional ads, 1991 (Box 236, Folder 6)
    - Jim Henson International Festival of Puppet Theater, 1998 (Box 236, Folder 7)
    - KDKA promotional contract, 1997 (Box 236, Folder 8)
    - Kid's Night on Broadway, 1997-1998 (Box 236, Folder 9)
    - Letterhead and invitation samples (Box 236, Folder 10)
    - Lila Wallace Planning Grant, 1997-1998 (Box 236, Folder 11)
    - Make a Wish, January 1998 (Box 236, Folder 12)
    - Market research zip code analysis, 1991-1992 (Box 237, Folder 1)
    - Market Square Association Marketing Plan by City Group (Box 237, Folder 2)
    - Marketing advisory committee, September 1997 (Box 237, Folder 3)
    - Marketing advisory committee, May 1998 (Box 237, Folder 4)
    - Marketing department's list of resources, May 1991 (Box 237, Folder 5)
    - Marketing settlements and ledgers, 1993-1997 (Box 237, Folder 6)
    - Marketing staff meeting notes, September 1994 (Box 237, Folder 7)
    - Marketing work plan, 1996 (Box 237, Folder 8)
    - Marketing work plan and advertising timelines, 1997-1998 (Box 237, Folder 9)
    - Martin Media, 1995 (Box 237, Folder 10)
    - Millennium Project, 1998-1999 (Box 237, Folder 11)
    - Musicals Alliance, 1996-1997 (Box 237, Folder 12)
    - National Printing Company, 1996 (Box 237, Folder 13)
    - New Image Press (Box 237, Folder 14)
    - Newsletter winter, 1993-1994 (Box 237, Folder 15)
    - Newsletter summer, 1994 (Box 237, Folder 16)
    - Newsletter fall, 1995 (Box 238, Folder 1)
    - Newsletter winter, 1996 (Box 238, Folder 2)
    - Newsletter fall, 1996 (Box 238, Folder 3)
    - Newsletter winter, 1997 (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - Newsletter summer, 1997 (Box 238, Folder 5)
    - the Observer promotional packet, 1994-1995 (Box 238, Folder 6)
    - Off-site storage files, 1988 (Box 238, Folder 7)
    - O'Reilly Theater groundbreaking event itinerary, April 1997 (Box 238, Folder 8)
    - PACE meeting, 1996-1997 (Box 238, Folder 9)
    - PACE meeting Broadway series, March 4 1997 (Box 238, Folder 10)
    - PACE meeting Broadway ticketing, March 4 1997 (Box 238, Folder 11)
    - PACE preliminary information on 1996-1997 and 1997-1998 Broadway Series seasons, 1995-1996 (Box 238, Folder 12)
    - PACE price and performance schedules for the 1996-1997 Broadway Series season, 1995-1996 (Box 238, Folder 13)
    - Parkvale Savings Bank, January 1995 (Box 238, Folder 14)
    - Natalie Petesch, 1996 (Box 238, Folder 15)
    - Photo processing (Box 238, Folder 16)
    - Pittsburgh articles in non-local publications, 1985-1997 (Box 239, Folder 1-2)
    - Pittsburgh Center for the Arts cultural awards dinner honoring Carol Brown, April 22 1995 (Box 239, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Downtown Partnership, 1994-1997 (Box 239, Folder 4-6)
    - Pittsburgh Downtown Partnership block party, July 7 1998 (Box 240, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh Downtown Partnership business improvement district, 1996 (Box 240, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh Downtown Partnership corporate identity manual, 1996 (Box 240, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Downtown Partnership Make a Night of It! promotion, 1996 (Box 240, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh Downtown Partnership marketing committee minutes, January 27 1997 (Box 240, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh Downtown Partnership marketing steering committee, January 16 1995 (Box 240, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh Downtown Partnership Sparkle Season, 1994-1995 (Box 240, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh Downtown Partnership Sparkle Season, 1995-1996 (Box 241, Folder 1-2)